Here's what I eat in a week as a busy girl.
Hi guys, it's Ashley.
It has been a minute since I have filmed a video.
Honestly, in this apartment, I feel like I've only been in freaking New York City for like two months out
Of the whole year.
I have been traveling nonstop, but I'm finally here.
So let's show you guys what I eat in an entire week.
It's already lunchtime, 3.30 PM.
I had a degenerate morning.
Where we jumping boys?
Hey, buddy.
Go back to school, huh?
Yeah knock down Kill this ass.
Don't touch my girlfriend Sausage egg avocado with spoiled mayo And I got an everything
Bagel, tofu cream cheese, avocado, onion, tomato, lettuce
But basically as you guys know I am always very very busy.
I do content creation full-time I also am the CEO of a business, a matcha business.
I'm also a full-time older sister I have eight children.
I also own a michelin star restaurant.
So it's very busy over here It is now midday.
I'm gonna have my midday pick me up.
I warmed up some milk with some jasmine pearls I'm obsessed with jasmine tea.
There's like little jasmine flowers in here and I just steeped it in some milk and steeping for a while
So now we're gonna make a matcha out of it guys.
The reason I am so busy is really my matcha business This is Nami.
Takes up literally 90% of my time, but I love it and it is truly my passion.
So I don't even mind
Best matcha of my life.
Jasmine plus matcha is like the best combo in the entire world Anyways, it is getting later in the day
And tonight I'm having my friends over for dinner We are making summer rolls and I need to go to
The grocery store and get all my ingredients together.
So let's go do that Okay, guys we are currently at the super market I am following a
Wild little Yo, you just fucking rammed it into the wood.
Are you serious?
My old little Yo, my depth perception is off bro.
I thought it was gonna go further than that Mini cucumber.
How many times have you bought those and they turn into rotten mush in the fridge?
Most of the time.
For the summer rolls.
Yeah, these are all looking really good.
Sliced carrot.
Shredded carrot.
Nice slice.
Cilantro.
My dad's least favorite food in the entire world.
Cabbage.
What did you just say?
That's going to be $20.
It's 99 cents per pound.
It's probably a 20 pound cabbage.
That's good.
We can't afford this.
This is me before I moisturize.
This is me after.
Basil.
Mint.
One two three four bro they eat so much of
This while we're in the grocery store right now I literally have a migraine and you guys might get ocular
Migraines I actually haven't had one in like literally maybe three or four months I think they're mostly onset by
Stress or if I eat shiitake mushrooms very random got one right now out of nowhere lost a lot of
My central visions I'm not vibing with this right now I feel like I literally can't see anything
I'm on the verge of
Pissing myself When Ashley has to buy the meat for her boyfriend When she has a
Migraine and she has to pee But she already invited everyone over to her house for dinner Where she's gonna
Have to cook the whole thing Bro, literally
Help?
Bro, I got in trouble for vlogging.
It says we missed out.
Look at this.
Oops, it looks like an item was missed.
Come on, bro.
Okay, we're making my classic tofu by slicing up firm tofu, and then I do soy sauce, maple
Syrup, Onion and garlic powder
Cheers
Yes, I did this
Dark chocolate
Oh
You can always text me and be like you're so cute and I'll be like oh my god I have
A boyfriend our dessert yeah
It's so divine no sugar needed still very sweet Mmmmm Yeah
I'm going
To
Take a picture of the
I'm going to go to the next place.
Place of Greenpoint apps.
They were like, wait.
Mm-hm.
So pretty.
Radio Bakery with the girls.
Cocoa food, chili, sandwich, cornbread.
Best cornbread you'll ever, ever, ever eat.
Allison got the same sandwich as me.
And then I got an heirloom tomato, feta, and mint sandwich.
Cheers.
Mmm.
It's pretty fire, no?
It is so fire.
That is what I needed.
This is really good.
The flavor is amazing.
Someone needs to do most underground bakery in New York City.
I'm sure you've never heard of it.
It's called Radio Bakery.
Remember how the feta mint?
I had the tofu.
Tofu, I think, was way better.
That's like a 10.
It's like literally so freaking good.
So flavorful.
Spicy, so flavorful.
And then the feta one.
Pretty good.
Really fresh.
But I feel like it's missing something.
Like once I had that one I'm like, oh, Ashley's sandwich sandwich was so freaking perfect explosion so this one
Seven and a half still really good okay allison's been dying for us to try these I feel like they're
A 12 out of 10 brown sugar cornbread oh my god what the hell is this even cornbread
It's literally like that's like the most decadent and amazing cornbread I've ever had in my life a layer of
Sugar on top is it a 12 out of 10 guys come on that's the best
Coconut matcha cloud I got a coconut matcha cloud Allison got iced americano turn out it's an iced
Americano do you like it?
It's good it's like a typical matcha coconut cloud it's like refreshing but it kind of just tastes like coconut
Water with heavy cream on it.
Pistachio cream and regular matcha latte.
Regular matcha latte?
It's good.
It has kind of like a jasmine flavor.
This one's really good and nutty.
Okay, I'm home, and what do you have for me?
The yummy stir!
Thank you!
It'll be my dinner.
Dinner?
Yeah, because I just ate lunch.
I have to go on three business calls in like two minutes.
I'm running so late.
I'm freaking out.
Mondays are Ashley's holiday.
I have two nami calls one interview about new youtube features.
You guys love ashley's new room that we rearranged Did you show them?
I didn't even mention it yet.
I'll show it in one second two hours of calls later Yeah, I'm literally ceo literally as kelly
Mentioned my room looks totally freaking different So let me show you surprise.
What the literal heck is this kelly and I a couple nights ago literally at 1 a.m We're
Like, what if you redo my room?
Here's what it looks like you guys know it used to be over here We removed parts of like the
Sides of my bed frame so it could fit in this little corner.
We are figuring out what's going on over here.
Desk in front of the window.
Let's go out and do the rest of my apartment.
It's literally glorious and it's golden hour.
And I need to clean up my kitchen a little bit, but this is freaking beautiful.
Time to eat my yummy stick dinner that Kelly got me.
I get the avocado yummy stick.
Yummy stick is our favorite sushi burrito place.
It's basically like kimbap like korean except the interior is japanese and the owners are korean and they are the
Nicest people in the entire world.
Cheers.
I got the avocado yummy stick
I have an ongoing debate with pelly right now that I can easily eat six yummy sticks and as I'm
Eating this right now I'm, like I can literally eat six of them and I said if I was like
Really competitively eating eight to ten And if it was life or death, I could eat 12 and nobody believes
Me.
Kelly's whole family They didn't believe me.
The only thing that's stopping me from not eating 12 yummy sticks is literally pure dedication Like I have to
Hold myself back.
You know what I'm saying?
So
Nobody freaking believes me.
Freakin' beasted.
I need five more right now.
Mini bowl of mini wheats.
I'm just craving cereal.
I woke up so hungry this morning.
So we're gonna put together a really simple plate of chia pudding I prepped this bowl of chia pudding a
Couple days ago.
It's literally just chia seeds and then this high protein soy milk that I got.
So it's been resting in the fridge for a while.
It's nice and thick now.
Now I'm going to rinse some berries, blackberries, raspberries, cherries.
And then I have some blueberries that I already washed.
Cheers!
Oh my god, it's still recording.
I'm freaking watching Cat's Eye React to Tate McRae.
Now heading to Pilates!
I'm home from Pilates.
I just ate an amount of Dubai chocolate that has made me feel ill.
I also just went to H-Mart.
I grabbed some Shine Muscat grapes.
$14 worth of grapes, which is crazy, but I love these grapes.
So I definitely need to make a matcha with it one of these days.
Let's rinse it.
As a little snack, as I prepare my lunch, these grapes are very popular in Korea.
And beverages, ice cream, everything.
Today, I am making solma noodles.
And in Korean, solma means, is this even real?
Like these noodles are so good.
Is it even real?
Is it even possible?
Okay now for the sauce we are going to use one tablespoon of honey one
And a half tablespoons of soy sauce and one tablespoon of sesame oil.
We also need garlic so I'm going to set this aside.
Add our soba and mix it all up.
You're also supposed to add seaweed into it but let's try it before we add any seaweed.
Cheers!
What the hell, it's so spicy.
Damn that's spicy!
Minion seaweed.
This is my first time having it, by the way.
I don't think I've ever heard of these.
They're popular on Korean television.
Seaweed on the bowl does look crazy.
Mmm!
What the heck?
It's a real- Hmm.
What do you think?
Yup.
Okay, the sharpie flavor is still there.
Like marker flavor.
And the other half is really yummy, like garlic, seaweed, soy sauce.
I feel like it's not supposed to taste like that.
It's still pretty good, but it has like really strong flavors that I don't think are intentional.
Yeah, I think I should have used different noodles.
Yeah.
And then the honey I used is like really organic, like strong honey.
I literally think it's going to take two days for the garlic flavor to come out of my mouth.
Matcha time!
One, because I want matcha, and two, because I'm fearful that the garlic breath is going to be irreversible and
Something needs to be done about it.
I always like to do half soy, half oat.
Adding our matcha.
Oh, there's not enough room for it.
Ah!
It's spilling it!
Mmm.
I used my Yame ceramic, but I'm actually drinking our Okumadori matcha today.
And we're going to have a little dessert.
Pastela bread.
Cheers.
An amazing combo.
Time for me to get ready for our dinner!
And also do some emails and work.
I picked up Amber's bag to see what's in her bag.
It's 100% empty except for one lip gloss and a portable charger
The little spin queen showed them to fit.
Hey So cute.
Here's my outfit of the day.
I got this in korea.
I forgot the name It's like eight seconds or something I'll put on screen damson matter my freaking cabbies.
They're destroying my feet Then forehead is from outer space Boom get roasted sunny studios.
Majuri and then this is mark sherwood I'm wearing a very Korean outfit low-key and all the funky pieces are
From damps and matter the jeans everything Steve Madden.
Yeah, I buy direct.
Let's go.
I'm Ambrose plus one
I've never opened a real one.
I only have the poof.
I want the orange one or the green one
We don't have any fructose!
We can pray!
Oh my god I love the hood!
Oh!
Okay we just had pasta I forgot to film it.
Oh my god I ate it all Oh you're canceled.
You didn't show your pasta that you ate for dinner?
I'm unsubscribing.
I can't trust you anymore.
Post-workout I'm having a koya vanilla bean protein shake that I freaking brought from my house and put it in
My bag why because it's like my favorite protein shake but also I want to go like do some work
At a cafe right now and the cafe doesn't have any food food so I'm prepared now I'm going to
Go get a pumpkin spice latte
Look
At my
Freaking home page what is this perhaps what is this secret I'm home I just took a
Shower I'm running so behind I'm supposed to film a youtube video I have to take a couple calls randomly
And then I have an event soon.
So I'm just eating my leftover noodles for lunch since I am starving.
So it's literally just soba, soy sauce, sesame oil, and a little pinch of maple.
Tastes way better than my garlic noodles from yesterday.
Okay, getting ready for my event tonight.
It is in fact a Dior event.
So I'm going to a little cocktail hour at their new house of Dior that's opening in New York.
They sent me a little gift.
It was like, I'll show you actually I put on my back.
Look at this little bee.
So cute.
It's like a little trinket.
Put it on there.
Now I have to go choose my outfit.
Here is my outfit for the event.
I'm wearing a little Dolce Vita flats.
My entire outfit is from my friend Michaela's brand called Twilum.
She is in fact an amazing designer.
How beautiful is this shirt?
It's like literally so insanely gorgeous.
The shorts are from there as well.
Then of course I have my bag from Dior.
And a jacket that I literally pretty thrifted.
Vintage Christian Dior jacket.
Are you serious?
So that's the vibes for tonight.
Let's head out.
Protein bar time.
Try not to eat too many protein bars if I can help it, but when I'm in need of eating
It, they are pretty freaking fire.
I actually eat granola bars all the time.
Oatmeal chocolate chip flavor.
Fanciness, huh?
The first thing that I've eaten here is a raspberry tart.
Cheers.
Mmm.
Mmm
Okay chocolate our time I'm only gonna eat half
Wait, it's spicy wait, it's actually really spicy or I'm having a lot going on
Hey, are we allergic to this but it was good though
I'm home!
I changed out of my outfit and I'm freaking starving to the point where I feel like I'm tweaking it
Out.
Today has not been so good on me eating good meals because literally all I had was protein
Smoothie, ran a bowl of noodles, granola bar, pumpkin spice latte.
I need to make dinner but I'm also so tired that I'm going to make a really easy dinner.
We are going to have some Korean black beans So basically you just need a can of black beans then
We're gonna wash and strain them the beans are washed So I'm gonna put it in some Tupperware then as
I've been doing for literally every single recipe in this video We're gonna add some soy sauce sesame oil
Pinch of agave and some garlic powder
Going out the soon tofu just like really soft tofu
A little bit of chili oil and all the same spices as the bean Maybe it's the Korean in me
But like garlic sesame soy sauce a little bit of sweetener It's literally the best thing ever give it a
Little chop.
I just need a cold Cheers
Like it's actually divine Wow whenever my sister and I make rice if we have any leftover We will freeze
It so that you have like these perfectly microwavable rice portions going in the microwave for for about a minute
And then I'll check on it.
Rice is perfect.
I'm gonna add that to the bowl.
Big.
Also gonna do some kimchi and some dak-gwon radish, aka daikon.
Guys, I'm sorry I have to do it.
Everything but the bagel seasoning going on the rice.
And this is what you call a Korean-American meal.
I feel like it's missing a little bit of sauce and I'm a sauce girl.
So in my dirty bowl I'm gonna whip up a random AF sauce.
Okay, let's use some gochujang gochujang miso paste garlic powder agave And sesame
Oil no soy sauce.
I feel like the miso is already kind of salty final pace.
Let's try it Add the sauce also on the rice and here is my finished
Bowl it looks freaking amazing Cheers mmm look through the beans are the best
Part I'm gonna chow down on this and probably have some fruits and maybe ice cream for my dessert
Good morning alright guys today I woke up early because I want to do like a full clean of my
House.
I'm making quick matcha.
I'm going to make a classic usucha aka I'm preparing matcha in the traditional Japanese way just simply
With water and biscuit.
I'm using our Okumadori first harvest matcha.
This one I really like if I'm having like plain just because it's a little bit more floral so I
Feel like it tastes more like tea undertones.
Now that I've whisked it, I'm gonna add some more hot water.
This is at about like a 165 and anywhere between 140 to 176.
It's supposed to be like that good range for matcha.
Ta-da!
Cheers!
This is my favorite way to drink it when I'm like, I need an energized morning.
Pure, clean energy with no crash and lots of antioxidants and L-theanine so you don't get
Jitters.
And then I'm gonna clean my freaking room.
And I'm gonna feel amazing.
So that's what I'm doing right now.
Finally, it's breakfast time!
Breakfast is served.
I made a very cutie bowl.
This is an Allison bowl, by the way.
I'm freaking Ali Wong, period.
We have chia pudding with bananas, white peaches, pistachio, cherry, honey, and hemp seed.
I feel very whimsical with this breakfast bowl, so let's dig in, shall we?
I changed my outfit I am wearing a little mock neck my levi's dolce vita shoes we're actually
Going to a levi's event right now so I'm very excited
We're going to a gifting suite every year we've been invited to levi's one it's like literally only one we
Go to once a year and it's so nice and they literally just give us freaking pants I got these
From here last year I think I bought these ones myself but they are from levi's
I'm leaving I got a scone it was like a peach vanilla scone Show me your little haul.
We got literally every pair of jeans in the freaking world.
Including a bunch for Kelly, Pono, and Andrew.
And our mom.
They were literally so nice in there.
They were like, you should get some for your mom.
You should get some for Pono.
What about Andrew?
What about Kelly?
I'm like...
Thank you, Kristen.
Thank you, girls.
Thank you, God.
Amber loves sosa.
We got some Filipino food from these stands right here.
This is longanisa, which is a sweet sausage.
This is really the best food in the world.
Okay, and then I got some ube toron.
Yes.
Cheers.
Love that stuff.
It's plantain and ube.
The ube is crazy with it.
Now we're about to go get some ice cream.
Their dark chocolate one is so good.
Cotton candy is fire.
Hazelnut is fire.
Cotton candy and hazelnut.
I always get the strawberry and then honey almond yogurt.
If I don't get this, I get their dark chocolate and it's so good.
Where you get Luke?
I got a cone.
We went to go to a fashion show but we were one minute too late so now we are
Waiting outside.
It was delicious and larches.
Yeah that was actually good.
It's a little grittier.
I feel portable but it's okay.
We missed the fashion show but it's okay because we are eating an awesome breakfast.
Now
Wait, do you just get sendy with an egg chugging challenge
Recording live from the hey tea my second time going in this video why because I'm freaking obsessed.
We have our kale tea, and then I also got the coconut mango blue.
That looks insane.
And spirulina mango boom.
It tastes probably freaking amazing.
Gimme that.
There are chunks of real mango in this that are like the most ripe and soft ever.
So good.
Wow, these are freaking amazing.
And for dinner we had Indian food, and it was so good that I'm literally craving it currently while editing
This video.
Anyways guys, thank you so much for watching.
I hope you enjoyed seeing what I eat in a week.
If you want more videos like this, let me know.
And I will see you guys next time.
Bye.